A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 4, Accession 4 FA1186
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges from China, 4
  The Exchanges from China series documents exchanges from 1973 to 1990. The range of delegation topics suggests a broad interest in these exchanges. Sports and martial arts featured in some of the early exchanges (Gymnastics, 1973; Wushu Troupe, 1974; Women's Basketball, 1975; Tennis, 1979). In 1978, the Performing Arts Company, composed of performers and artists from the Beijing Opera and the China National Ballet Troupe, toured the U. S. to great acclaim. Other delegations studied foreign language publishing and teaching (1973-1980s); education; journalism, radio and television broadcasting, and press law; government, law, justice, and foreign relations; economic planning and development. The China International Travel Service delegation traveled in 1978; a Women's Delegation in 1979; and the Chinese People's Committee for the Defence of Children visited in 1980. Other files concern Civil Engineering and Architectural Education and Urban Design delegations in 1981.
  The dates listed for Exchanges files generally refer to the trip date. They do not reflect the exact date range of the contents.
  - Mayors Delegation - Environmental Conference, 1990 July 7-26 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - China Press Law Research Centre Delegation - General, 1990 June 23-July 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Postponed from 1989.
  - China Press Law Research Centre Delegation - Background Readings, 1990 June 23-July 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - China Press Law Research Centre Delegation - Visits (Correspondence), 1990 June 23-July 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Training Center for Senior Judges Delegation, 1988 October 11-November 8 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Training Center for Senior Judges Delegation, 1988 October 11-November 8; FA1186:001 (Box 61)
    2 matte proof sheets of candid shots of delegation's visit to New York State Office of Court Administration, New York.
  - Ministry of Justice Delegation, 1985 June 1-11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Special Economic Zones Delegation, 1985 March 6-21 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Forensic Medicine Delegation, 1985 January 19-February 10 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Language Publishing Delegation - General, 1985 January 9-27 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Language Publishing Delegation - Visits, 1985 January 9-27 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences (Canceled), 1984 December 9-21 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Language Teachers Study Team, 1984 November 10-30 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Provincial Editors Delegation, 1984 October 24-November 11 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Provincial Editors Delegation, 1984 October 24-November 11; FA1186:002 (Box 61)
    6 color slides from delegation visit to Savannah harbor.
  - Xinjiang Science and Technology Delegation (Visits), 1984 October 6-27 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - State Planning Commission Delegation - General, 1984 April 11-29 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - State Planning Commission Delegation - Visits, 1984 April 11-29 (Box 3, Folder 17-19)
  - Foreign Policy Think Tanks Delegation, 1984 March 28-April 15 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Central Institute of Educational Science - General, 1984 February 29- March 22 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Central Institute of Educational Science - Visits, 1984 February 29- March 22 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Humanities Education Study Team, 1984 February 15-March 8 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - City of Beijing Friendship Delegation (Mayor Chen Xitong), 1983 November 27-December 3 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - UNICEF Children's Radio and Television Broadcasting Delegation, 1983 November 8-24 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - State Economic Commission and China Enterprise Management Association Delegation - General, 1983 October 12-November 3 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - State Economic Commission and China Enterprise Management Association Delegation - Visits, 1983 October 12-November 3 (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
  - State Economic Commission and China Enterprise Management Association Delegation - Visits, 1983 October 12-November 3; FA1186:003 (Box 61)
    3 color snapshots of delegation at Disneyland
  - Higher Education Administration Study Team - General, 1983 September 14-October 6 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Includes Report on China Visit, by D. F. Finn, 1982 December 28 (visit to China).
  - Higher Education Administration Study Team - Visits, 1983 September 14-October 6 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - State Council Economic Law Delegation (Gu Ming) - General, 1983 June 12-July 2 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - State Council Economic Law Delegation (Gu Ming) - General, 1983 June 12-July 2; FA1186:004 (Box 61)
    5 color snapshots of delegation in Washington, DC, and 2 duplicates.
  - State Council Economic Law Delegation (Gu Ming) - Visits, 1983 June 12-July 2 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - China Daily Delegation, 1983 June 2-18 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Zhongshan University (President Huang Huanqiu) Delegation - Itinerary, Background, and Planning, 1983 May 5-June 26 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Zhongshan University (President Huang Huanqiu) Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1983 May 5-June 26 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Han Ji (Xi'an Urban Planning Bureau) Visit, 1983 April 20-May 8 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Cross-Cultural Training Study Team, 1983 April 6-28 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing Delegation (Canceled April 7, 1983), 1983 April 5-7 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - UNICEF Children's Science Pictorial Delegation, 1983 March 20-April 2 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Journalists Delegation - General, 1982 November 3-25 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Still Image - 1 Polaroid image of delegates at unidentified meeting.
  - Journalists Delegation - Visits, 1982 November 3-25 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Intensive English Language Training Study Team, 1982 November 3-25 (Box 5, Folder 43-44)
  - Archivists Delegation - General, 1982 September 30-October 23 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Archivists Delegation - Visits, 1982 September 30-October 23 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Delegation:General, 1982 June 23-July 15 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Delegation:Visits, 1982 June 23-July 15 (Box 6, Folder 48-49)
  - Science Education Delegation, 1982 May 15-June 5 (Box 6, Folder 50-51)
  - Historians Delegation, 1982 March 31-April 15 (Box 7, Folder 52-53)
  - Chinese Language Teachers Delegation:, 1982 March 24-April 15 (Box 7, Folder 54-55)
  - Television Cultural Study Team, 1982 January 13-February 4 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Minister of Education Delegation - General, 1980 June 4-20 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Minister of Education Delegation - Visits and Thank Yous, 1980 June 4-20 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Diving Team, 1980 April 21-May 6 (Box 36, Folder 347)
  - Provincial Governors Delegation - Namelists, Itinerary, Guidelines, 1980 October 20-November 6 (Box 36, Folder 348)
    Also called Provincial Leaders Delegation.
  - Provincial Governors Delegation - Background and Planning, 1980 October 20-November 6 (Box 36, Folder 349)
  - Provincial Governors Delegation - Report, 1980 October 20-November 6 (Box 36, Folder 350)
  - Provincial Governors Delegation - Visits and Local Itineraries, 1980 October 20-November 6 (Box 36, Folder 351-353)
  - Provincial Governors Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1980 October 20-November 6 (Box 36, Folder 354)
  - Beijing Institute for International Strategic Studies (BIISS) Delegation, 1982 June 22-29 (Box 36, Folder 355)
  - Beijing Institute for International Strategic Studies (BIISS) Delegation (Supplemental Material), 1982 June 22-29 (Box 36, Folder 356)
    Global Political Assessment 13 (October 1981 - April 1982); Herman Kahn, "The Nature and Feasibility of War, Deterrence, and Arms Control," May 1982.
  - Gymnastics Team Visit - General, 1973 May 18-June 5 (Box 36, Folder 357)
  - Gymnastics Team Visit - Press Coverage, 1973 May 18-June 5 (Box 37, Folder 358)
  - Gymnastics Team Visit - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1973 May 18-June 5 (Box 37, Folder 359)
  - Journalists Delegation - Itinerary, Background, and Planning, 1973 May 17-June 15 (Box 37, Folder 360)
    Visit hosted by the American Society of Newspaper Editors (ASNE).
  - Journalists Delegation - Namelists, 1973 May 17-June 15 (Box 37, Folder 361)
  - Journalists Delegation - Visits and Local Itineraries, 1973 May 17-June 15 (Box 37, Folder 362-364)
  - Language Teaching Study Group - Background and Planning, 1973 November 8-December 14 (Box 37, Folder 365)
  - Language Teaching Study Group - Itinerary and Schedule Planning, 1973 November 8-December 14 (Box 37, Folder 366)
  - Language Teaching Study Group - Visits and Local Itineraries, 1973 November 8-December 14 (Box 38, Folder 367-369)
  - Language Teaching Study Group - Visits and Local Itineraries, 1973 November 8-December 14; FA1186:017 (Box 61)
    Photo of delegation members descending from Hawaiian Airlines plane.
  - Language Teaching Study Group - Reports, Final Itinerary, and Namelists, 1973 November 8-December 14 (Box 38, Folder 370)
  - Language Teaching Study Group - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1973 November 8-December 14 (Box 38, Folder 371)
  - Wushu Troupe - General, 1974 June 21-July 14 (Box 38, Folder 372)
  - Wushu Troupe - Visits and Local Itineraries, 1974 June 21-July 14 (Box 38, Folder 373-374)
  - Wushu Troupe - Visits and Local Itineraries, 1974 June 21-July 14; FA1186:047 (Box 62)
    Wushu of China Program, New York City Center, for performances June 24 and June 25, 1974 (2 broadside programs)
  - Wushu Troupe - Visits and Local Itineraries, 1974 June 21-July 14; FA1186:048 (Box 62)
    Poster, Wushu of China, Benefit Opening NIght by Friend of the Chinese Culture Foundation, Masonic Auditorium, San Francisco, June 28, 1974.
  - Wushu Troupe - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1974 June 21-July 14 (Box 38, Folder 375)
  - Wushu Troupe - Program Booklet, 1974 June 21-July 14 (Box 39, Folder 376)
  - Wushu Troupe - Program Booklet, 1974 June 21-July 14; FA1186:018 (Box 61)
    4 8x10 negatives of Wushu moves. Images used in souvenir booklet of the delegation's visit to San Francisco.
  - Wushu Troupe - Program Booklet, 1974 June 21-July 14; FA1186:019 (Box 61)
    3 pages of headshot photos of Wushu delegation (44 images); plus 3 copy prints of same. Images reproduced in Program Book and in San Francisco souvenir booklet.
  - Wushu Troupe - Press Coverage and Clippings, 1974 June 21-July 14 (Box 39, Folder 377-378)
  - Wushu Troupe - Other Visits, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 379)
  - Performing Arts Troupe - General, 1975 March 29-April 27 (Box 39, Folder 380)
  - Performing Arts Troupe - General Planning, 1975 March 29-April 27 (Box 39, Folder 381)
  - Performing Arts Troupe - Host Committee and Visit Arrangements, 1975 March 29-April 27 (Box 39, Folder 382)
  - Performing Arts Troupe - Host Committee and Visit Arrangements, 1975 March 29-April 27; FA1186:042 (Box 62)
    Oversize: Poster for Performing Arts Troupe, Chicago, April 11-13, 1975
  - Performing Arts Troupe - Press Coverage, 1975 March 29-April 27 (Box 39, Folder 383)
  - Performing Arts Troupe - Tour Cancellation, 1975 March 29-April 27 (Box 39, Folder 384)
    Correspondence and press coverage.
  - Performing Arts Troupe - Tour Cancellation (Board Members' Response), 1975 March 29-April 27 (Box 39, Folder 385)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Trip Arrangements Notebook, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 40, Folder 386)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Background and Planning (General), 1975 November 15-30 (Box 40, Folder 387)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Background and Planning (General), 1975 November 15-30; FA1186:020 (Box 61)
    19 Headshot photos of team members and staff.
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women (AIAW), 1975 November 15-30 (Box 40, Folder 388-389)
    Correspondence and financial accounting, 1975-1977.
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Correspondence with Chinese, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 40, Folder 390)
    Includes team roster with photos of coaches and players.
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Program Brochure, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 40, Folder 391)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Program Brochure, 1975 November 15-30; FA1186:043 (Box 62)
    Oversize: Pen and ink drawing of logo (probably for cover of program book for November 22 game).
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Travel Schedules and Itineraries, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 40, Folder 392)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Los Angeles, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 40, Folder 393)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Memphis, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 40, Folder 394)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Rochester, NY, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 40, Folder 395)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Rochester, NY, 1975 November 15-30; FA1186:021 (Box 61)
    Group photo of U. S. Women's Basketball Team
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - New York City, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 41, Folder 396)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Washington, D.C., 1975 November 15-30 (Box 41, Folder 397)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Press Releases and Clippings, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 41, Folder 398)
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Press Releases and Clippings, 1975 November 15-30; FA1186:022 (Box 61)
    4x5 black and white photo of Chinese coach hugging American player after game
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Press Releases and Clippings, 1975 November 15-30; FA1186:044 (Box 62)
    Oversized: Broadside photo spread from Chinese paper on Women's Basketball Team visit.
  - Women's Basketball Team Visit - Follow-Up, 1975 November 15-30 (Box 41, Folder 399)
    Includes evaluation.
  - Performing Arts Company - Background and Planning, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 42, Folder 413-415)
  - Performing Arts Company - Guidelines, Itineraries, and Schedules, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 42, Folder 416)
  - Performing Arts Company - Schedules, Stage Requirements, Contacts, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 42, Folder 417)
  - Performing Arts Company - Contracts and Budget, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 43, Folder 418)
  - Performing Arts Company - Contributions and Money Sent to the Metropolitan Opera Association, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 43, Folder 419)
  - Performing Arts Company - Paper on Chinese Opera as Instrument of Social Change, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 43, Folder 420)
    Unidentified paper, circa 1973. File also includes copies of letter addressed to "Member, Chinese Group," which were sent to their hotel and dropped in the orchestra pit.
  - Performing Arts Company - Program Booklets, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 43, Folder 421-422)
  - Performing Arts Company - Program Booklets, 1978 July 1-August 8; FA1186:024 (Box 61)
    2 sets of photos of opera and ballet (13 black and white of the Ballet Troupe's performance of "The White Haired Girl," and 17 color prints of Peking Opera and musicians).
  - Performing Arts Company - Television File, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 43, Folder 423)
  - Performing Arts Company - Tickets for Board, Members, and Friends, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 43, Folder 424)
  - Performing Arts Company - Dress Rehearsal (July 3), 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 43, Folder 425)
  - Performing Arts Company - New York, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 43, Folder 426-427)
  - Performing Arts Company - New York Reception (July 5), 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 44, Folder 428)
  - Performing Arts Company - Newport Opera Festival invitation, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 44, Folder 429)
    Includes 4 black and white photos of Opera Festival productions and artwork (retained in file).
  - Performing Arts Company - Washington, DC, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 44, Folder 430)
  - Performing Arts Company - Washington, DC, Reception (July 18) and Tickets, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 44, Folder 431)
  - Performing Arts Company - Minneapolis, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 44, Folder 432)
  - Performing Arts Company - San Francisco, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 44, Folder 433)
  - Performing Arts Company - Los Angeles, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 44, Folder 434)
  - Performing Arts Company - Thank Yous, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 45, Folder 435)
  - Performing Arts Company - Press Coverage and Publicity, 1978 July 1-August 8 (Box 45, Folder 436-437)
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Itinerary, Guidelines, Namelist, and Brochure, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 47, Folder 468)
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Background and Planning, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 47, Folder 469)
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - New York, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 48, Folder 470)
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Philadelphia and Swarthmore, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 48, Folder 471)
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Philadelphia and Swarthmore, 1978 March 30-April 20; FA1186:026 (Box 61)
    Arthur Rosen being introduced to Adele Rickett, with Mr. Yuan Ch'ao-chun.
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Washington, DC, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 48, Folder 472-473)
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Memphis and Arkansas, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 48, Folder 474)
    Still Images: 3 color photos of Greers Ferry Lake. Not separated (separation number 2015:045:031 suppressed).
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Houston, Phoenix, Grand Canyon, Los Angeles, and Yosemite, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 48, Folder 475)
    Still Images: 10 photos (color and black and white) of Yosemite landscapes. Not separated (separation number 2015:045:030 suppressed).
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - San Francisco, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 48, Folder 476)
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Publicity, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 49, Folder 477)
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Publicity, 1978 March 30-April 20; FA1186:046 (Box 62)
    Oversized: 3 issues of China Daily News, March 30, April 3, and April 4, 1978. April 4 issues includes article on the delegation; contents of other issues unknown.
  - China International Travel Service (Luxingshe) Delegation - Thank You Letters and Follow Up, 1978 March 30-April 20 (Box 49, Folder 478)
  - Municipal Administrators Delegation - General, 1978 September 10-30 (Box 49, Folder 479)
  - Municipal Administrators Delegation - Washington, DC, 1978 September 10-30 (Box 49, Folder 480)
  - Municipal Administrators Delegation - New York, 1978 September 10-30 (Box 49, Folder 481)
  - Municipal Administrators Delegation - Minneapolis, Dallas, and San Francisco, 1978 September 10-30 (Box 49, Folder 482)
    Still Images: 2 black and white photos of power substation, Pacific Gas and Electric, San Francisco.
  - Municipal Administrators Delegation - Thank Yous, 1978 September 10-30 (Box 49, Folder 483)
  - People's Daily Delegation - General, 1979 January 7-27 (Box 49, Folder 484)
  - People's Daily Delegation - Visits and Thank Yous, 1979 January 7-27 (Box 49, Folder 485)
  - Foreign Trade Education Study Group, 1979 April 6-May 1 (Box 50, Folder 486)
  - Foreign Trade Education Study Group, 1979 April 6-May 1; FA1186:027 (Box 61)
    37 images (3.5 x 5, black and white and color, mounted on pages) from Ernst & Ernst seminar for the China Foreign Trade Education Study Group.
  - Theater Equipment Study Delegation (Ministry of Culture) (Cancelled), 1979 April-May (Box 50, Folder 487)
  - Provincial Education Delegation - General, 1979 May 13-June 2 (Box 50, Folder 488)
  - Provincial Education Delegation - Visits, 1979 May 13-June 2 (Box 50, Folder 489)
  - Provincial Education Delegation - Thank Yous, 1979 May 13-June 2 (Box 50, Folder 490)
  - Women's Delegation - General, 1979 May 19-June 7 (Box 50, Folder 491)
  - Women's Delegation - Visits, 1979 May 19-June 7 (Box 50, Folder 492)
  - Women's Delegation Press Clippings, 1979 May 19-June 7 (Box 50, Folder 493)
  - Women's Delegation - Questionnaire, 1979 May 19-June 7 (Box 50, Folder 494)
  - Women's Delegation - Report, 1979 May 19-June 7 (Box 50, Folder 495)
  - Women's Delegation - Follow-Up Reports and Correspondence, 1979 May 19-June 7 (Box 50, Folder 496)
  - Ta Kung Pao Visit, 1979 June 9-July 8 (Box 51, Folder 497)
    Visit of Li Tsung-ying and Tsang Tak-sing.
  - Tennis Delegation, 1979 August 16-September 3 (Box 51, Folder 498)
  - Business Management Delegation - General, 1979 October 7-November 4 (Box 51, Folder 499)
  - Business Management Delegation - Background and Planning, 1979 October 7-November 4 (Box 51, Folder 500)
  - Business Management Delegation - Visits, 1979 October 7-November 4 (Box 51, Folder 501-502)
    Includes Brookings Institution Conference on American Political Institutions and National Economic Policy Making.
  - Business Management Delegation Follow Up; Thank-You, 1979 October 7-November 4 (Box 51, Folder 503)
  - Television and Radio Broadcasting Delegation - General, 1979 October 31-November 21 (Box 51, Folder 504)
  - Television and Radio Broadcasting Delegation - Washington, DC, and New York, 1979 October 31-November 21 (Box 51, Folder 505)
  - Television and Radio Broadcasting Delegation - Columbus, OH - Los Angeles, 1979 October 31-November 21 (Box 51, Folder 506)
    Columbus, Chicago, Iowa, San Francisco, and Los Angeles.
  - Television and Radio Broadcasting Delegation - Thank Yous, Report, and Follow-Up, 1979 October 31-November 21 (Box 51, Folder 507)
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defence of Children (UNICEF Delegation) - General, 1980 March 5-26 (Box 52, Folder 508)
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defence of Children (UNICEF Delegation) - Background and Planning, 1980 March 5-26 (Box 52, Folder 509)
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defence of Children (UNICEF Delegation) - Visits, 1980 March 5-26 (Box 52, Folder 510-511)
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defence of Children (UNICEF Delegation) - Visits, 1980 March 5-26; FA1186:028 (Box 61)
    3 color negative strips (10 images) of delegation visit to Seattle. Sent by Carol Knudson to Janet Cady, June 3, 1980.
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defence of Children (UNICEF Delegation) - Visits (Seattle), 1980 March 5-26; FA1186:029 (Box 61)
    Group photo of delegation at dinner hosted by Dr. Frank Brouillet, State Superintendent of Public Instruction, March 7, 1980, Olympia, WA.
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defence of Children (UNICEF Delegation) - Visits (Denver), 1980 March 5-26; FA1186:030 (Box 61)
    8 black and white 5x7 prints of delegation visit
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defence of Children (UNICEF Delegation) - Visits (Boston), 1980 March 5-26; FA1186:031 (Box 61)
    Group photo of delegation, taken on occasion of luncheon hosted by Women in Development, Boston, March 18, 1980
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defence of Children (UNICEF Delegation) - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1980 March 5-26 (Box 52, Folder 512)
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defence of Children (UNICEF Delegation) - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1980 March 5-26; FA1186:032 (Box 61)
    13 snapshots (color and black and white) of delegation visit (plus some duplicates); color and black and white negative strips.
  - Henan Province Delegation - General, 1980 April 20-May 14 (Box 52, Folder 514)
  - Henan Province Delegation - Visits and Press Coverage, 1980 April 20-May 14 (Box 53, Folder 515)
  - English Language Teaching Delegation, 1981 February 18-March 12 (Box 53, Folder 520-521)
  - Civil Engineering and Architectural Education Study Team - General, 1981 February 18-March 12 (Box 53, Folder 522)